do you know how sick in the head you have to be to hate miss rachel only a demon will demonize
a human being for wanting kids to live so basically the zionists are saying
that to want palestinian kids to live is anti-semitic do they even listen to themselves
she's basically saying that it is blood libel against our zionist jewish supremacide
for you to want palestinian children to live oh live in such a cocoon bubble of zionist privilege
on this power trip that they can say what they want get away with what they want persecute who
they want and not fear the consequences that's the freaking world we live in they even labeled
miss rachel top anti-semitic of the year now ladies and gentlemen ladies and gentlemen let me set you
free you shall know the truth and it shall set you free it is a badge of honor to be called an
anti-semitic by zionist jews let me say that again let me say hello it is a freaking badge of honor
to be called an anti-semitic by zionist jews because it means you're doing it right you're
resisting right you're fighting right you're pushing back right you're being the voice of the
voiceless your fearlessness is what they fear that in spite of their zionist power construct you are
holding your head up high and you refuse to be on the side of history that says yes to genocide
yes to cruelty yes to evil yes to an ideology of supremacy that has no place in our society
so if you don't have that badge of honor yet you best go get it let's be clear it is not anti-semitic
to be anti-killing children it is not anti-semitic to be anti-zionist it is not anti-semitic to be
anti-israel it is not anti-semitic to be anti-genocide it is not anti-semitic to be anti-ethnic
cleansing it is not anti-semitic to be anti-starvation it is not anti-semitic to be anti-rape
it is not anti-semitic to be anti-apartheid it is not anti-semitic to be anti-state terrorism
and quite frankly it is not anti-semitic to not give a rat to us about the fragility and supremacy
of walking talking zionist oppressors masquerading as victims people let the truth set you free so
the truth the whole truth and nothing but the truth is that the only people that should be on
a big bright banner of anti-semit of the year are zionists let me say it again i'll say it again
the only people that should be on a big bright banner of anti-semitic of the year are zionists
because they are the ones hijacking the jewish identity and weaponizing the jewish faith for
nefarious purposes like genocide and weaponizing anti-semitic to further zionism we see you
we know you and we are not scared of you